Welcome to the hardware files for Antumbra Beta!  You're probably a little crazy 
about Hardware if you decided to dig this far!

Our hardware source is offered under GNU GPL - see below.

This product is open hardware: you can redistribute it and/or modify
    it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
    the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
    (at your option) any later version.

    The source files are distributed in the hope they will be useful,
    but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
    MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
    GNU General Public License for more details.

    Please see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.

Here you'll find:
-Gerber files.  These are what you need to get PCBs produced.  
	-Also included:  centroid "pick and place" file.  	
-Bill of Material (BOM) in both PDF and CSV formats.  Buy those parts!
-Diptrace Schematic File (.dch)
-JPG schematic image
-Diptrace PCB file (.dip)
-JPG PCB image (contrast)
-Some .stl files to 3D print your own case (we recommend Shapeways if you don't
have your own printer)
-Some images of hardware assembly. 

We chose diptrace as a CAD program to help insure that our files are still accessible
to the general population.  Diptrace has a freeware version, and also great student
deals on the "pro" version - download it to edit the files.  

A note on producing the hardware:  low tolerances are not well tolerated by the LED, we recommend a high-resolution SLA / SLS printer if possible.  Most FDM printers are not high-res enough to create a proper device.  In addition, you will need a bumper material to support the board - these bumpers should be cut to about 5mmX5mm squares with about 1/8th to 3/16ths of an inch uncompressed height.  This material (as well as all other materials) should be rated for 100C or more, and should have an adhesive back with the same or greater rating.  We highly recommend 3/16ths thick “very soft” poron foam - McMaster PN:  86375K141. In order to affix the device to the back of a monitor, we recommend either velcro, 3M dual lock, or 3M VHB adhesive.  Adhesives and fasteners should be rated for 85C+ (such that they don’t fail due to device heat).  

Although we strongly advocate for making and hardware hacking, we accept
no responsibility for 3rd-party produced Antumbra Glow units, including devices
you may produce yourself.  The LED consumes a non-trivial amount of power, and
improper design, production or assembly could be dangerous.

That's all!  Have fun.


